(Sheldon:)The two of them
now share a coffee can
(Sheldon:)on my mother's mantel.
(Howard:)So I knocked down
the bathroom door,
(Howard:)picked up my poor
unconscious mother,
(Howard:)carried her to the car,
(Howard:)and drove like a madman
to the emergency room.
(Bernadette:)You're a real
hero, Howard.
(Howard:)No, I did what
any son would do.
(Penny:)Hang on a second--
you picked up your mother?
(Penny:)Her own legs
are barely able to do that.
(Howard:)I was filled
with adrenaline.
(Howard:)It happens to be how women
lift cars off babies.
(Penny:)Yeah, I'm saying,
it'd be easier to lift a car.
(Howard:)What can I tell you?
After I found the courage
(Howard:)to put her pants back on,
I was unstoppable.
(Leonard:)So, how is she?
(Howard:)They're running tests--
I don't know.
(Howard:)It may have been a heart attack
or heart-attack-like event.
(Penny:)What's the difference?
(Sheldon:)A heart-attack-like event
(Sheldon:)is an event
that's like a heart attack.